HAYLEY BUDZINSKI

Aurora, CO 80014 · (907) 350-4298

hayleybudzinski@gmail.com · GitHub: https://github.com/hmbudzinski

I am an experienced professional with a demonstrated history of working in a variety of administrative, clerical, and customer service-based positions. I am currently in school part time earning a certificate in web development and coding, while working full time.

EXPERIENCE

OCTOBER 2019 - PRESENT

PARALEGAL, HOFFMAN NIES DAVE & MEYER, LLP

- Independently correspond with and maintain client relationships
- Draft, review, and revise Estate Planning Documents
- Assist in the formation of Nonprofits and LLCs
- Maintain attorney schedules and coordinate client meetings
- Daily use of Outlook, Microsoft Word and Excel, Tabs Billing System, Adobe Acrobat

MARCH 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2019

PARALEGAL, WHITE BEAR ANKELE TANAKA & WALDRON, P.C.

- Research and data collection and tracking using Practice Master and other data tracking tools for over 130 Metropolitan Districts around Colorado
- Draft, review, and revise contracts and agreements
- Track annual compliance matters and statutory deadlines
- Coordinate attorney schedules and client meetings
- Daily use of Outlook, Microsoft Word and Excel, Practice Master, Tabs Billing System, Adobe Acrobat

SEPTEMBER 2015 - OCTOBER 2016

SUPERVISOR, BUNSEN BURGER, DUBLIN, IRELAND

- Ensure open communication among staff and customers
- Organize and operate multiple restaurant management systems
- Handling guest and employee complaints and comments
- Comply with financial transaction policies
- Monitor all operations including monetary transactions, employee hours, and distribution of tips

EDUCATION

APRIL 2020

FULL STACKED WEB DEVELOPER CERTIFICATE, UNIVERISTY OF DENVER

This is a six-month intensive bootcamp where students become proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, API's, React.js, Node.js, MySQL, and other programming languages and applications.

MAY 2014

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN INTERNATIONAL STUDIES, COLORADO STATE UNIVERSITY

I completed a four-year Bachelor of Arts Degree with a major in International Studies and a minor if International Development.

SKILLS

- Knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Node.js
- Desire to Learn
- Punctual and Passionate
- Maintains Positive Attitude in stressful situations
- Strong Work Ethic

- Technical Knowledge of Microsoft Applications
- Ability to Work in a Team and Independently
- Problem-solving and Decision-making
- Written and Verbal Communication

ACTIVITIES

In addition to having a passion for finding where I belong in my career, I also really enjoy rock climbing, the outdoors, and traveling the world. I have been lucky enough to travel to 29 countries working in different hostels and through educational opportunities and I do not have any intention of stopping. While I do enjoy the world outside of the United States, since moving back to Colorado in 2017 I have developed a new found love for exploring my own backyard.